<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Wise Analytica</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Wise Analytica</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aru Bhardwaj</title>
      <link>/team/aru-bhardwaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aru-bhardwaj/</guid>
      <description>Aru is the founder of Wise Analytica. Started his career as a data science consultant in 2019, since then he is working with clients across the globe. He is experienced crafting machine learning solutions for different sectors including management consulting firms, marketing agencies, real estate firms and healthcare institutions. He believe that the most important trait in a data scientist is not how well one implements the algorithms and models but translating a real-life problem that can be solved using that analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>/services/nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/nlp/</guid>
      <description>Natural language processing is increasingly becoming a dominant solution across different industries.
Natural language processing (NLP) is an AI technology that enables computers to understand human language. NLP is used in a variety of industries, including healthcare, finance, customer service, and more.
Healthcare: NLP is used in healthcare to extract information from clinical documents, such as patient records and discharge summaries. This information can be used to improve patient care, track disease outbreaks, and inform research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics and Reporting</title>
      <link>/services/datanalytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/datanalytics/</guid>
      <description>In the business world, data is everything. It helps you understand your customers, your products, and your market. And in today’s digital age, there is more data available than ever before. But as any business owner knows, data is only valuable if you can make sense of it. That’s where data analytics and reporting comes in. By analyzing data and creating reports, businesses can gain insights that they can use to make better decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Extraction and Prepration</title>
      <link>/services/dataextraction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/dataextraction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/services/machinelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/machinelearning/</guid>
      <description>Machine learning is a rapidly growing field with many potential applications in areas such as finance, healthcare, transportation, and more.
For Business Machine learning is a process of teaching computers to learn from data, without being explicitly programmed. This is done by feeding the computer large amounts of data, and allowing it to find patterns and insights in the data. The computer can then use these patterns and insights to make predictions or recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey Analytics</title>
      <link>/services/surveyanalytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/surveyanalytics/</guid>
      <description>If you want to keep your business relevant and top-of-mind for your customers, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand what they want and need. Luckily, with survey analytics, you can learn a lot about your customers in a short amount of time. Survey analytics can help you understand your customers better, so you can make changes to your sales and marketing strategies accordingly. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore some of the ways survey analytics can benefit your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Architecture</title>
      <link>/services/dataarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/dataarch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Wise analytica was created in 2022 with the aim of helping businesses and communities make better decisions with their data. We believe that data should be used to its fullest potential in order to create a more stable and efficient world.We offer a wide range of services including data analytics, data science consulting, and data visualization. We work with clients of all sizes, from small businesses to large organizations. Our team of experts has a wealth of experience and knowledge in the field of data analytics and is ready to help you achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Book a free consultation call using this link
   Day Working Hours (GMT)     Tuesday 8:00am - 7:00pm   Wednesday 8:00am - 7:00pm   Thursday 8:00am - 7:00pm   Friday 8:00am - 7:00pm   Saturday 8:00am - 7:00pm    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
